So, please introduce yourself.
じゃあ、自己紹介をお願いします
Mami Tamiya, 22 years old, is from Gifu Prefecture.
タミヤ・マミ、22歳、岐阜県出身です
This is Mami Tamiya.
タミヤ・マミさんですね
Please give me a call.
おかけください
Yes, please excuse me.
はい、失礼いたします
Have you interviewed at a few companies yet?
面接はもう何社か回ってますか?
Well, I'm currently visiting several companies.
そうですね、何社か回ってて今
How many times did you go around?
どのくらい回られましたか?
We visited 100 companies.
100社回りました
It went around quite a bit.
結構回りましたね
Are you used to interviews?
面接は慣れたもんですか?
Something you’re used to?
慣れたもの?
I'm having a hard time getting used to it.
なかなか慣れないです
You can feel the tension.
緊張感が伝わってきますからね
The company culture is kind, so you don't have to be nervous.
一応ね、優しい社風なので、緊張しなくていいですから
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is there anything Tamiya is good at?
タミヤさんは得意なものとかありますか?
What are you good at?
得意なもの?
Do you have any hobbies?
趣味とかありますか?
My hobby is reading.
趣味は読書です
Are you reading?
読書ですか
yes.
はい
It gets read a lot.
結構読まれるんですね
I agree.
そうですね
How many books do you read per week?
週に何冊くらい読んだりしますか?
I guess it's about 2 books.
2冊くらいですかね
I guess it's something to be read carefully.
結構じっくり読まれるほうなんですかね
Can I ask you to tell me what other companies you interviewed for?
他にはどんな会社を面接したか教えてもらってもいいですか?
For reference.
参考までに
Health foods, etc.
健康食品とか、
Pillow company, manufacturing pillows.
枕 会社、枕の製造
Yes, yes.
はいはい
Are you new?
新入ですかね
I agree.
そうですね
Are there any manufacturers that specialize in pillows?
枕に特化したメーカーもある?
yes.
はい
Of course I think we understand,
うちは、もちろん分かると思うんですけど、
You know what company it is, right?
何の会社かは分かってますよね
It's underwear, right?
下着ですよね
We don't really make underwear for men, we mainly make underwear for women.
男性向けはあまり作ってなくて、女性向けの下着がメインに作って
Masu.
ます
By the way, do you have any of our underwear?
ち なみに、弊社の下着はお持ちでしょうか?
I don't have it.
持ってないです
Oh, I don't have it.
あら、持ってない
I wonder why I don't have it.
どういった理由で持ってないのかな
What reason?
どういった理由
It's a bit expensive for students.
ちょっと、学生さんにしては高いからですからね
Well, it's a bit pricey.
そうですね、ちょっと値段が
Oh, is that so?
ああ、そうですか
No, I'm sorry, but neither does my company.
いや、すみませんね、うちの会社もね
Ah, that's nice.
あ、いいですね
We don't make it at a reasonable price either, so it's more of a luxury item.
リーズナブルも作ってないので、高級趣向なものですからね
The design is tailored to women, so
デザインもご婦人方に合わせているので、
It just didn't seem suitable for young children.
若い子にはちょっと合わない感じでしたからね
From now on, I will incorporate the opinions of young people like Mr. Tamiya.
これからは、田宮さんみたいな若い方の意見を取り入れてですね、
I'm thinking of making one.
作っていこうかと思いますので
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Well, we're also developing underwear.
まあ、下着も開発していくんですが、
Mr. Tamiya, do you know how many cups of underwear you have?
田宮さんは下着何カップか分かりますか?
I think it was B.
Bだったような
Oh, haven't you measured it properly?
あ、ちゃんと測ったりはしてないですか?
I agree.
そうですね
Also, you have to wear something that suits your body.
あと、自分の体に合ったものをつけないとですね
It's bad for your body, and it also has something to do with your posture.
体に悪いというか、姿勢とかにも関わってくるので
The shape of your breasts may also change.
胸の形も変わってきたりしますからね
First of all, would you mind taking off your jacket for a moment?
まずは、上着をちょっと脱いでいたらいいですかね
It's foldable.
折っかちですね
There's a button.
ボタンがありますよ
Please let me know.
お伝えください
sorry.
すみません
That's proactive.
積極的ですね
That's good, Tamiya-san.
いいですね、田宮さん
sorry.
ごめんなさい
That's proactive.
積極的ですね
Is it blue?
ブルーですか?
About something like a ribbon.
リボンみたいについて
It looks like hair.
髪らしいですね
yes.
はい
Did you choose and buy it yourself?
今、ご自分で選んで買われたんですか?
When you saw it at the store, what did you like about it before you bought it?
お店で見て、どういったところが気になって買いましたか?
I'm curious about the design.
デザインが気になるところ
What parts of the Citi Bar will change?
シーティーバーどの部分って変わりますか?
I really like the design of this part.
ここの部分のデザインがすごい気になる
It looks a bit like hair.
ちょっと髪らしいですもんね
It looks like there's a little gap.
少し隙間があるように見えますね
That's right.
そうなんです
Excuse me.
失礼します
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Please make your hands comfortable.
手を楽にしてくださいね
It's floating in the gap.
隙間浮いてますね
Let me check the bag.
袋を確かめさせてもらいます
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Doesn't the fabric rub against your neck and cause pain?
生地は首首に擦れて痛くなったりとかないんですか?
Not really.
ないですね
It's a good material.
良 い素材ですね
Would you like me to show you the one below?
下の方、見せてもらいますか?
The lower one.
下下の方
Can I take off my shoes?
靴脱いでもいいですか?
That's fine.
いいですよ
Can I have you stand for a moment and give me some guidance?
ちょっと立っていただいて、 指導も向いてもらっていいですか?
Can I show you this?
これで見せてもらっていいですか?
Yes, that's fine.
はい、いいですよ
That's good.
いいんですね
Everyone, what are your hobbies in underwear?
みなさん、下着の趣味とかも、
Here you can find underwear that fits your body properly.
ここ はちゃんと自分の体にあった下着を、
I'm also writing a check based on what I'm wearing, so
履いているところからチェックも書いているので、
That's nice.
いいですね
Did you also play sports?
スポーツでもやってましたか?
I've done it in the past.
過去にやってました
You're muscular.
筋肉されていますね
is that so?
そうですか?
Is there one?
あるんですか?
Then stockings.
じゃあストッキング
Look at the chest and torso.
胸胴を見ますからね
I'll give you our stockings on the way home.
帰りに弊社のストッキングを渡しますから
yes.
はい
It broke easily.
簡単に破れちゃいましたね
It's stretchy.
伸縮性がありますね
Does this have anything to do with the interview?
これって面接に関係あるんですか?
yes.
はい
I want you to cry.
泣いて欲しいですよね
I agree.
そうですね
There is also Bobil.
ボビルもあるんですね
yes.
はい
You have beautiful feet.
綺麗な足になっていますね
yes.
はい
Is there a connection?
関係あるんですか?
We have to keep an eye on the health status of those who become our employees.
社員になる方の健康状態を 見ておかないといけないですから
hey.
ね
A while ago.
ちょっと 前に
Sorry.
すいません
I'll be waiting.
待ってます
待って ます
Does this have anything to do with the interview?
これって面接に関係あるんですか?
I want you to cry.
泣いて欲しいですよね
yes.
はい
I want it.
欲しいですね
I need to check the thickness at the bottom as well.
下の厚みも調べないと
Is the fabric thin?
生地が薄いんですか?
Is it thin?
薄いんですかね
It hits the poor side.
貧乏なところに当たってますね
I'm right.
当たってます
So the fabric is thin.
じゃあ生地が薄いんですね
What is Tamiya's poverty?
タミヤさんの貧乏なところは?
A poor place.
貧乏なところ
What do you call this place?
ここは何と言いますか?
picture?
え?
Is it a clit squirrel?
クリットリスですかね
I won't be able to cry if you don't give me a proper answer.
ちゃんと答えてくれないと 泣いてあげられませんからね
yes.
はい
Does the clitoris feel good?
クリットリスは気持ちいいですか?
Yes, it feels good.
はい、気持ちいいです
How does it feel good to touch you?
どういうふうに触れると気持ちいいですか?
Clitoris is.
ク リットリスは
The clit feels good.
クリットリスは気持ちいいです
It's getting wet right now.
すぐ濡れてますね
Are you wet?
濡れてます?
yes.
はい
Can you see it?
見えます?
It's pulling.
引いてますね
Why are you so wet?
なんでこんなに濡れてるんですかね
What is it?
なんなんですか
It's just an interview, though.
ただの面接なんですけどね
yes.
はい
Do you have a body that gets excited easily?
興奮しやすい体なんですかね
that's right.
そうです
Oh, is that so?
ああ、そうなんですか
I could easily get my finger in it.
簡単に指が入っちゃいました
Does everyone shed tears?
みなさん、お涙とかはしますか?
Yes, I will.
はい、します
Where do you often touch when you cry?
お涙の時は、どこをよく触りますか?
middle?
中?
Do you want to touch inside?
中を触りますか?
Is this the case?
こういう具合ですか?
Yes, that's what it feels like.
そう、そういう感じです
How many times a week do you do it?
週に何回ぐらいするの?
About 3 times a week.
週に3回ぐらい
That's nice.
いいですね
Healthy.
健康的で
I'm going in the middle of an interview, so
面接の最中に行っちゃうので、
His body is quite developed.
す いぶん体が発達されてるんですね
He's a good boy.
いい子ですよ
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
It's just an interview.
ただの面接です
Yes, yes.
はい、はい
What do you think?
どうですか?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Check for sweat spots.
汗がついているところを確認します
He doesn't seem to be sweating.
汗がかいていないようです
Huh, huh?
えっ、えっ
The construction is getting really stiff.
すごい作りが固くなってきてますよ
yes.
はい
Does it get hard where it feels good?
気持ちいいところが固くなるんですか?
I agree.
そうですね
yes.
はい
Try touching yourself.
自分に触ってみてください
Yes, yes.
はい、はい
Can I talk to you?
話しちゃってもいいですか?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい、ごめんなさい
There are now two people.
2人になりました
Does Amiya have any experience with men?
アミヤさんは男性経験はあるのかな?
there is.
あります
How many people did you like?
何人ぐらい好きだったのかな?
Three people, three people.
3人、3人です
So you're already doing this?
じゃあこんなことはもうしてるんだね
yes.
はい
What kind of sex do you like?
どんなセックスが好きなのかな?
what kind?
どんな?
What kind of sex are you having?
どんなセックスしてるんだい?
yes.
はい
Are you having your boobs licked or your pussy licked?
おっぱい舐められたり、 おまんこ舐められたりしてるのかい?
yes.
はい
They did me a good favor.
ちゃんと善意はしてもらってくれた
that's right.
そうです
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Is Edge usually seen like this?
普段のエッジはこんなに見られたりするのかな?
yes.
はい
Being licked,
舐められたり、
Say this...
こう いう...
picture?
え?
Have you ever used toys?
おもちゃが使ったことあるのかい?
there is.
あります
There is.
あるんだ
What kind of toys do you like?
どんなおもちゃが好きとかあるのかい?
What kind of toy?
どんなおもちゃ?
This kind of massage,
こういうマッサージのやつだったり、
yes.
はい
The one that puts it in the pussy,
おまんこにズボズボ入れるやつだったり、
yes.
はい
What kind of toys do you like?
どんなおもちゃが好きなのかな?
Yeah.
うん
It's a massage.
マッサージです
massage.
マッサージ
Is this it?
これか
yes.
はい
Are you hitting a place that feels good?
気持ちいいとこに当たってるかい?
Please answer whether it feels good or not.
気持ちいいとこ当たってるかとか答えなさい
I hit a spot that feels good.
気持ちいいとこ当たってます
Are you getting it right?
ちゃんと当たってるかい?
I'm right.
当たってます
Guess it yourself.
自分で当ててください
By yourself?
自分で?
yes.
はい
It felt good.
気持ちよかったです
It's not annoying.
うざくないと
yes.
はい
Can I make it annoying?
うざくさせることができるかな?
yes.
はい
The way I use it is really good.
うちの使い方が上手だね
is that so?
そうですか?
In reality, you've dealt with a lot of dicks, haven't you?
本当はたくさんのチンチンを相手にしてきたんじゃないかい?
I won't.
しないですよ
Please cry.
泣いてください
How about raw chin chin?
生のチンチンはどうだい?
It's my first time.
はじめてね
It feels so good.
とても気持ちいいです
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Hey, hey, roll?
ね、ね、転がる?
roll?
転がる?